<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Latest From Red Stick Chick on Red Stick Chick</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in The Latest From Red Stick Chick on Red Stick Chick</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Seasonal Decor</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/seasonal-decor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/seasonal-decor/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Celebrate the Easter holiday by bringing it into your home! Maybe you&amp;rsquo;re weary of winter and are excited to see signs of spring. Maybe the discipline and faith-building season of lent brings you joy and the sight of Easter decor reinforces that. Maybe you just like cute chicks and bunnies! Let me help you brighten your home or event with flowers and decor as you celebrate the season.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Event staging</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/event-staging/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/event-staging/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I offer expert staging for holiday-themed home décor, creating beautifully styled spaces that capture the magic of the season. Whether you’re looking for a cozy, traditional Christmas setup, a chic and modern holiday look, or festive décor for any special occasion, I design and arrange decorations that transform your home into a warm and inviting space. From elegant tablescapes and statement centerpieces to wreaths, garlands, and twinkling lights, I bring a touch of seasonal charm to every corner. Let me take care of the details so you can enjoy a stress-free and stunning holiday atmosphere!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charcuterie boards</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/charcuterie/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/charcuterie/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Imagine transforming any special occasion into a gourmet experience with beautifully crafted charcuterie boards made fresh onsite! With an eye for detail and a passion for quality ingredients, I bring a personalized touch to every event—whether it’s a wedding, corporate gathering, or intimate celebration. Using an array of artisanal cheeses, cured meats, fresh fruits, nuts, and gourmet accompaniments, I design stunning boards tailored to your theme and guest preferences. Guests get to enjoy the freshest flavors and a beautiful presentation. Elevate your next event with an onsite charcuterie experience that blends artistry, taste, and elegance in every bite!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Going Away Party</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/party/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/party/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Let me take the stress out of planning a going-away party by designing and executing a personalized send-off that perfectly captures the guest of honor’s journey ahead. From selecting a meaningful theme and crafting stunning decorations with thoughtful touches, I ensure every detail reflects their unique story. Whether it’s an intimate farewell dinner, a lively gathering with friends, or a travel-inspired soirée, I handle logistics, setup, so you can focus on making memories. With creative vision and seamless execution, I’ll create a heartfelt and unforgettable farewell celebration tailored to your needs!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prom, dances, and youth socials.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/youth-events/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/youth-events/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I offer exceptional staging and decoration services to transform proms, dances, and youth socials into unforgettable experiences! From elegant and glamorous prom themes to fun and energetic social events, I bring creativity and attention to detail to every celebration. From stunning backdrops, themed centerpieces, balloon arches, draping, and interactive décor that sets the perfect mood, we can bring your vision to life. Together, your event will be beautifully staged, seamlessly decorated—creating a night to remember for everyone involved&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A special wedding</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/wedding/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/wedding/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I enjoy creating elegant bridal bouquets, stylish boutonnieres, and charming small centerpieces for intimate weddings. Each floral arrangement is thoughtfully designed to complement your theme, color scheme, and personal style, adding a touch of beauty and romance to your special day. Whether you’re planning a cozy backyard wedding or a small, elegant gathering, I provide high-quality, fresh flowers that enhance your celebration without overwhelming your space. Let me bring your floral vision to life with stunning, handcrafted designs tailored just for you!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
